cowbird.com 2019-06-17

# Cowbird ·

This policy applies to your use of the Cowbird Services and website (collectively, “ _Cowbird_ ”), regardless of how they are accessed. If you do not agree with this privacy policy, do not access or use Cowbird. 

##  Information that Cowbird Collects 

Flaming Toast Productions, LLC. (the “ _Company_ ,” “ _us_ ,” “ _we_ ”) collects personal information when you register with Cowbird, when someone invites you to join Cowbird, and when you use, access, or visit Cowbird. When you register we ask for certain information such as your name and email address. When you register with Cowbird and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. Cowbird is not intended for children under the age of 13. 

The stories, sounds, images, and other media content (“Content”) that you submit for inclusion in Cowbird may reveal personal information about you and the subjects of that Content. We ask that you obtain permission from others and that you carefully consider the information that you want to disclose about yourself and others in the public forum that Cowbird provides. Please be thoughtful and decent. Once you choose to share Content through Cowbird, that Content could potentially be copied and reshared by others with access to Cowbird. 

Cowbird automatically receives and records information from your computer/mobile device and browser, including your IP address/device ID, cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request. Cowbird may set and access Cowbird cookies on your computer. Cowbird may use web beacons and other technologies to track your use of Cowbird. 

It is possible that others may submit Content that provides links to sites and services outside of Cowbird, and this privacy policy does not apply to such third party sites and services. Additionally, some of the services included on Cowbird are delivered or served by third-party companies that may place or recognize cookies, web beacons or other technology to track certain information about our Web site users. For example, we may include in Cowbird certain integrations with third-party social networks. In the course of serving certain third-party social network functionality on Cowbird, some third-party social network operators may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser in order to collect certain information about your use of Cowbird. In many cases, this information could be used to show you ads based on your interests on other Web sites. 

We do not have access to, nor control over, third-party companies' use of cookies or other tracking technologies or how they may be used. 

##  How Cowbird Uses and Discloses Information 

The Company uses (or may choose to use) your information for the following purposes: to customize Content you see on Cowbird, to fulfill your requests for products, services and information, to respond to questions and concerns that you have submitted to us, to improve Cowbird, to communicate with you, and to provide anonymous reporting for internal and external persons. 

The Company does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except: (a) to provide products or services that you’ve requested, or (b) if you choose to make such personal information available as part of the Content that you have submitted for use and/or display on Cowbird, or (c) when we have your permission, or (d) under any of the following circumstances: 

We provide certain information to service providers who work on behalf of, or with, the Company to help us provide Cowbird and to communicate with you. 

We provide information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal requirements, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 

We provide information when we believe it may be useful to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, fraud, threats to the safety of any person or property, violations of Cowbird’s [Terms of Service](http://cowbird.com/terms/), or as otherwise required by law. 

We would transfer information about you if the Company (or Cowbird) is acquired by or merged with another company or reorganizes itself into another company. In this event, Cowbird will attempt to notify you before information about you becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

##  Your Ability to Edit Your Information 

You can access and edit your account information through Cowbird. You can also opt out of receiving future messages (including the “Cowbird Daily Story” email), but we reserve the right to continue to send you certain communications relating to Cowbird, such as service announcements and administrative messages, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. 

You can delete your Cowbird account. Please click here to read about information that might possibly remain on Cowbird or in our archived records after your account has been deleted. 

##  Confidentiality and Security 

The Company limits access to personal information about you to employees, contractors and service providers who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide Cowbird services to you or as otherwise provided in this privacy policy. 

We have physical and technical safeguards designed to protect personal information we maintain about you. However, notwithstanding these safeguards, unauthorized persons may access your personal information and account. We cannot promise that your personal information will always be secure. 

##  Changes to the Cowbird Privacy Policy 

The Company may update this privacy policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Cowbird account and/or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

##  International Users 

Users from outside the United States should be aware that they are submitting their information to servers within the United States and that they may not be entitled to the protections and remedies provided for under the laws of their places of residence. 

##  Questions and Concerns? 

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, please contact us. 

**By mail:**  
Flaming Toast Productions, LLC.  
Attn: Cowbird  
P.O. Box 235  
Shelburne, VT 05482 USA  
Attn: Privacy Concern 

**By email:**  

_THIS PROCESS IS FOR COPYRIGHT AND OTHER INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY MATTERS ONLY. For reports of abuse and related concerns, please see the links provided for in the[Cowbird Etiquette](http://cowbird.com/etiquette/). _

Flaming Toast Productions, LLC. and its affiliates respect the intellectual property of others, and we ask our authors to do the same. We may, in appropriate circumstances and at our discretion, disable and/or terminate the accounts of authors who may infringe or repeatedly infringe the copyrights or other intellectual property rights of Flaming Toast Productions, LLC. and/or others. 

In accordance with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act of 1998, the text of which may be found on the U.S. Copyright Office website at <http://www.copyright.gov/legislation/dmca.pdf>, Cowbird will respond expeditiously to claims of copyright infringement committed using the Cowbird service if such claims are reported to Cowbird’s Designated Copyright Agent as identified below. 

If you believe that your work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, or that your intellectual property rights have been otherwise violated, please provide our Copyright Agent for Notice with the following information in English (your "Notice"): 

  * an electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright or other intellectual property interest 
  * a description of the copyrighted work or other intellectual property that you claim has been infringed 
  * a description of where the material that you claim is infringing is located on Cowbird, with enough detail that we may find it on the website (in most circumstances, we will need a URL) 
  * your address, telephone number, and email address 
  * a statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright or intellectual property owner, its agent, or the law 
  * a statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in your Notice is accurate and that you are the copyright or intellectual property owner or authorized to act on the copyright or intellectual property owner's behalf. 
  * _Note: If you are asserting infringement of an intellectual property right other than copyright, please specify the intellectual property right at issue (for example, ‘trademark’)._

In some circumstances, in order to notify the user, account holder or host who submitted the allegedly infringing content to which we have disabled access in response to a Notice, Flaming Toast Productions, LLC. or its designee may forward a copy of a valid Notice including name and email address to the user or account holder, or others in its discretion. Your Notice is not private information, and we may choose to post a copy of your Notice, with your personal information removed, on Cowbird and/or to [Chilling Effects](http://www.chillingeffects.org/) for publication and/or annotation. 

Cowbird's Designated Copyright Agent can be reached as follows: 

**By mail:**  
Flaming Toast Productions, LLC.  
Attn: Cowbird  
P.O. Box 235  
Shelburne, VT 05482 USA  
Attn: Copyright Agent 

**By phone:**  
(781) COW-BIRD  
(781) 269-2473 

**By email:**
